<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Tribal Defences (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.TribalDefences</packageId>
  <author>Rimrue</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/TribalDefences</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Rimrues mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947686580

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/TribalDefences][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
Adds tribal defences to the game:

-Earthen mounds (provide more cover than rock chunks, but less than sandbags, constructable on diggable terrain)
-Tribal Helmet (a wooden tribal helmet, requires Smithing research)
-Tribal Armor (a tough hide coat with wooden slat armor, requires Smithing research)
-Great Bow and Pila constructable at Crafting Spot (requires Smithing research)
-Spear constructable at the crafting spot (requires no research)
-Pitfall Trap (a deep pit with pointy spikes at the bottom, requires Basic Traps research)

To add:

-Bow trap (made with either a great bow or a short bow, the tribal version of turrets, requires Basic Traps reasearch).

-----

Credits in no particular order:

* Tribal armor breastplates by 3DGrunge

* Earthen Mounds texture by CuproPanda

* Pitfall Traps by Bacon Bits https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=25708.msg260860#msg260860

-----

Or go for the full Tribal experience with my Tribal Essentials Modpack, which combines this mod, my other two tribal mods, plus more!

http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=928716116

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>
