<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Tribal Essentials Reborn</name>
  <author>Zaljerem</author>
  <supportedVersions>
     <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>zal.tribalessentials</packageId>
  <loadAfter>
	<li>zal.smokedmeat</li>
	<li>dracoix.zars.spots</li>
	<li>PrimitiveProduction.velcroboy333</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>

Original mod by RimRue - latest version by dracoix
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1820484592
(dracoix kindly gave permission for me to continue this mod)


Tribal Essentials Reborn! My impatient fork of the long-running Tribal Essentials/Tribal Reborn/ZARS Tribalism mod. It's gone through at least three authors and multiple "official" and "unofficial" ports, why not another?

I was trying to be patient and wait for the ZARS Tribalism update (or splitting off, or whatever they had planned to do with it) - so to pass the time I started looking at the mod, cleaning it up, I created a spin-off Smoked Meat mod, updated the TribalInstruments mod, noticed in passing that Mlie had updated an old, old RimRue mod (that was absorbed into Tribal Essentials a few versions later anyway) and I figured - now is the time. Better to ask for forgiveness than permission. Besides, I missed the enhanced Tribal capabilities.


Mod details:

I removed all "Tribal Raiders" integration/assemblies. I figure that, other than the "tribal planet" option, there's really no need for it anymore with raider tribal factions in Core.

Patches for the Stone Oven, ZARS Production Spots, etc. are all still included and appear to be working correctly. All items except smoked meat (smoked meat, smokepit) have been retained.

Smoked meat has been removed as I reworked it in my mod "Zal's Smoked Meat". If that is installed before this mod, all of its capabilities should be available and the Stone Oven will be able to smoke meat, fish (if you have either RF OR Vanilla Expanded OR Thanks For All The Fish fishing mod earlier in your mod order) and fungus (if you have Ideology DLC).

I have added the integrations with Primitive Workbenches as found in that mod for ZARS Tribalism. Please load this mod AFTER Primitive Workbenches for this to activate.



Recommended mods to enhance your Tribal experience:
ZARS Production Spots - absolutely essential
ResearchPal - Forked - cleans up research tree
Zal's Smoked Meat
TribalInstruments (Continued)
Tribal Signal Fire (Continued)
Tribal Jewelry - appears to work in 1.3 though not officially updated yet

Mods that look good but I haven't tried:
Primitive Workbenches 
Primitive Storage
Primitive Tools


Credits:

"Tribal Essentials" - "Tribal Reborn" - "ZARS Tribalism"

ORIGINAL AUTHORS: RimRue [A17], Rainbeau Flambe [B18], dracoix [B19 - 1.2]

Detailed credits:

- 3DGrunge (Tribal Armor Breastplates)
- Bacon Bits (Pitfall Traps)
- CuproPanda (Earthen Mounds)
- ItchyFlea (Log Walls)
- MasterDihtung (Pottery)
- Mouf (Psychoid Tea and Patchwork Leather) (leather deprecated)
- Tammabanana (Smokepit) 
- Telkir (Stone and Wood Floors)
- TrueDestroyer (Double Sleeping Spot) (deprecated - now in Core)
- Hydromancerx (Primitive Floors)
- Diana (Kitty) (Animal Hoods)
- RimRue and Rainbeau Flame (Tribal Raiders) (integration now deprecated)
- Fierydraken (Hay Skirt)
- RimRue, for putting it all together in the first place!
- Rainbeau Flambe for porting it to B18
- dracoix for porting it to B19
- Midnight for unofficially porting it to 1.0
- dracoix for officially porting it to 1.0 - 1.2


Further information and older notes can be found in the About folder within the mod itself.


</description>
</ModMetaData>