<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Pocket Sand</name>
	<author>Usagirei</author>
	<packageId>usagirei.pocketsand</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>Pocket Sand!
	
Surprise your enemies with that weapon in your pocket.

Adds a gizmo to equip/unequip weapons to and from pawn inventory, that's it.

No tool auto-switching based on job/distance.
No pawn remembering what gear it had equipped and getting stuck on a equip-unequip loop when it tries to store its active weapon on a locker then dying of hunger.
Just a few buttons to manually equip a gun, knife, or what have you.

Similar to the old SimpleSidearms, when there wasn't a pawn memory, but even lightweighter.

Combat Extended Compatible.

Load Before Combat Extended

Changelog:
2021-07-16:
	• 1.3 Support
	
2021-06-05:
	• Changed mass-check behaviour to not allow pickup if the pawn is over capacity, instead of if pawn would be over capacity.

2021-05-29:
	• Gizmos now work when multiple pawns are selected, allowing for batch equipment changing.
	• (Optional) Added Replacement Caravan unload jobs, to prevent pawns from unloading their weapons.
	• (Optional) Added Replacement Equip/Unequip jobs, to enable a delay on equipment swapping. Picking up new equipment from the floor will now store the currently held one to inventory.
	• (Optional) Added a carry capacity check to prevent pawns from picking up weapons while over-encumbered. Only applies to equipment on floor.
	• Added Mod Configuration Menu, for the above options.
	• Still no actual sand included.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Core</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
	</loadBefore>
</ModMetaData>